henrico.k12.va.us 2003-06-21

# Disclaimer & Privacy Statement

3820 Nine Mile Road  
Richmond, Virginia 23223-0420  
(804) 652-3600 | 

**Disclaimer & Privacy  Statement **  
  
---|---  
  
_**PRIVACY STATEMENT**_

It is the policy of Henrico County Public Schools that personal information about citizens will be collected only to the extent necessary to provide the service or the benefit desired by the user; that only appropriate information will be collected; that the user shall understand the reason the information is collected and be able to examine their personal record.

This website:

1\. Collects no personal information.  
2\. Does not place a "cookie" on your computer.  
3\. Will not track your movements through the website.

_**DISCLAIMER**_

Some Henrico County Public Schools web pages have links to web sites "outside" of the HCPS web site. If you click on these links to visit other sites, you are subject to the privacy policies of those sites while you are visiting them, rather than the HCPS policies. 

Please note that by clicking on these links, you will leave the HCPS web site and enter a privately  
owned web site created, operated and maintained by a private business.

The information that this private business collects and maintains as a result of your visit to its web site may differ from the information that the HCPS collects and maintains (please see the HCPS web site  privacy notice for privacy protections HCPS provides to web site visitors).

By linking to this private business, the HCPS is not endorsing its products, services, or privacy or security policies. We recommend you review the business's information collection policy or terms and conditions to fully understand what information is collected by this private business
